

Toronto, ON Canada

GitHub: github.com/vhok

Email: victorhok@outlook.com Website: www.victorhok.com LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/victorhok

### **ABOUT ME**

I am a process-oriented Web Developer with experience in the Aerospace industry as an Analyst and an Engineering background. I bring experience developing responsive web applications using JavaScript, React, HTML, CSS, troubleshooting and solving technical problems and creating user-focused solutions from scratch.

## **SKILLS**

- HTML5, CSS3, Sass
- Responsive Design
- WCAG / Accessibility
- BEM Naming Pattern
- JavaScript
- jQuery, React
- REST APIs, Firebase
- C#, VBA, .NET Framework
- Batch, Makefiles

- Project Management
- Leadership
- Customer Service
- Paired / Group Programming
- GitHub / Version Control

# **EDUCATION**

## JUNO COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY

Certificate of Web Development (Full time),

Web Development 101 (Part time)

Mechatronics Option with Co-op

THE UNIVERSITY OF BRITISH COLUMBIA Sep 2009 - Dec 2015 Bachelor of Applied Science – Mechanical Engineering

# MY DEBUG PAL

**PROJECTS** 

React | Firebase | REST API | Sass | BEM | CSS3 | HTML5

bit.ly/mydebugpal

Jul 2020 - Jan 2021

A React based bug tracking app that allows users to submit an issue against my git repository. Uses GitHub API to retrieve most recent project list and firebase for managing the reading/writing/modification of issues.

## **SPORT SPOT**

Pair Coding | JavaScript | ¡Query | REST API | Sass | BEM | CSS3 | HTML5

bit.ly/thesportspot

A sports locator app that allows users to locate sports facilities for a variety of sports anywhere in the world. The final result is displayed in a gallery of cards containing map and address information.

## EEG (BRAIN SIGNAL) CONTROLLED FLAPPY BIRD GAME

Pair Coding | C# | COM | .NET Framework | PuTTY | NeuroSky API

bit.ly/bci-flappybird

Inspired by flappy bird, this mechanical video game utilizes EEG (brain) signals read through a head mounted device to control the height of a ping pong ball and navigate through obstacles.

## **POSITIONS HELD**

# **BOMBARDIER AEROSPACE** | Toronto ON | Methods Analyst

Sep 2017 – Jun 2020

- Led the internal auditing process of over 900 process control documents and 15 employees for aircraft assembly. As a result, manufacturing license for the Global 7500 aircraft program was maintained.
- Led 3 afternoon shift teams, provided training, oversight and direction on assignments.
- Developed repair manuals leading to the salvage of damaged components worth over \$5 million.

# ABI LTD. | Richmond Hill ON | Project Manager

Jul 2016 - Aug 2017

- End-to-end management of 10 projects leading to revenues of over \$4 million.
- Utilized root cause analysis to solve technical challenges across various technologies such as ultrasonic cutting, waterjet, and robot automation. Enabled company to meet quality requirements of customers.